TRI AJI RAMADHAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | FRONTEND ENTHUSIAST

CONTACT DETAILS

Address: Gg. Karya III RT07/RW09 No. 12, Menteng Atas, Kec Setia Budi, Jakarta Selatan

Contact: +62 857 4758 9814 Email: triajidhan@gmail.com Instagram: @ramadhantriaji Linked In: Tri Aji Ramadhan

Github: https://github.com/triajidhan **Portfolio**: https://triajidhan.github.io

SHORT PROFILE

I am a software developer who has the ability and experience in designing, developing and testing websites with the latest technology. I can work individually or in a team, and easily adapt to the environment. I am the type of person who works hard.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Physics Tutor

One Learning Center | Contract | December 2019 - June 2022

- Teaching physics using national, national+ or Cambridge Curriculum depending on the student's school (remote and offline)
- Some of my students come from SMAK 1 Penabur and St Laurencia

Video Solution Maker

Co-learn | Part-time | June 2021 - December 2021

- Create video solutions of physics subject for junior high, senior high, and UTBK level
- Award: Best video of the month (on October, 2021)

Software Developer

Lawencon International | September 2022 - Now

- Collaborate with other programmers and stakeholders to meet the requirements, objectives and functional aspects of the project.
- Manage corporate websites from designing, publishing, optimizing responsive websites on various browsers.
- Develop website from backend to frontend using Including desired relevant work experience.

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

SoloLearn.com

June 2022 | HTML, CSS, Javascript & JQuery

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019 • Diponegoro University

Material Physics

Departement of Physics, Science and Matematics Faculty | Diponegoro University Bachelor of Science

Ungradutate Thesis: "Numerical Analysist of Electric Polarization in Ferroelectric Thin-Film" by MATLAB

2012 - 2015 • SMA N 1 Kesesi

Natural Science

Third best graduate of natural science study program
Third place in the 2014 Pekalongan district physics OSN selection

SKILLSHEETS

HARD SKILLS

Java Springboot
Json Web Token (JWT)
Angular
ReactJs
PostgreSQL
NgRx
Redux
PrimeNg
PrimeFlex
Angular Material UI

- Miguiai Materiai O

Bootstrap

SASS

SOFT SKILLS

Teamwork
Communication
Adaptability
Problem Solving
Creativity
Leadership

LANGUAGES

indonesia : Native or bilingual proficiency
English : Limited working proficiency

INTEREST

In my sphere time, I personality enjoy learning about software developer and digital painting to upgrade my skills.

PROJECT

Dentistry Documentation | Frontend Developer | 2023

Project Description

Dental record of the patient. Information contained in the application, such as medical history, extra-oral and intra-oral examinations, dental odontograms, and patient care records.

Job Description

Manage corporate websites UI from designing, publishing, optimizing responsive websites on various browsers.

Tools

Angular, NgRx, PrimeNg, PrimeFlex

Learning Management System (LMS) | Support Frontend Developer | 2023 Project Description

Module at LinovHR to upgrade the skills of employees by participating in learning or courses that are held online or offline.

Job Description

Solve some bug from Quality Assurance at UI website LMS and create some UI page with angular.

Tools

Angular, PrimeNg, PrimeFlex

Back Office | Frontend Developer | 2023

Project Description

Manage the module package rental records at LinovHR. Includes access rights from a Tenant and its Companies to each CRUD of several modules in the application.

Job Description

Upgrade UI website from Angular 8 to Angular 14.

Tools

Angular, PrimeNg, PrimeFlex

Ticket Management System | Frontend Developer | 2023

Project Description

Records of complaints from clients about applications that are leased by clients. Manage complaint tickets starting from entering the IT consultant, to the Developer then to Quality Assurance.

Job Description

Manage corporate websites UI from designing, publishing, optimizing responsive websites on various browsers.

Tools

Angular, PrimeNg, PrimeFlex

Asset Management System | Fullstack Developer | 2022

Project Description

Manage assets owned by the company from leasing assets to returning assets with maturity.

Job Description

Manage corporate websites from backend to frontend designing, publishing, optimizing responsive websites on various browsers.

Tools

Java Springboot, PostgreSQL, Angular, PrimeNg, Bootstrap

Lawencon Int. Community | Frontend Developer | 2022

Project Description

Community, social media and market place for all Lawencon International employees. There are buying and selling events and courses so that employees can improve their skills.

Job Description

Manage corporate websites UI from designing, publishing, optimizing responsive websites on various browsers.

Tools

Angular, PrimeNg, PrimeFlex

E-Learning | Fullstack Developer | 2022

Project Description

Learning management system where lecturers can create several classes along with assignments for those classes. Students can join classes created by teachers and collect assignments from those classes.

Job Description

Manage corporate websites from backend to frontend designing, publishing, optimizing responsive websites on various browsers.

Tools

Java Springboot, PostgreSQL, Angular, PrimeNg, PrimeFlex